Is
the product
interesting? Totally
subjective. They
will
not know
the answer
to that.
How
do
you define
interesting? Something
new about
it,
is something
advanced about
it,
is something,
do I
think it's
gonna
be popular?
Do I
think it's
gonna flop?
A lot
of products
are just
kind
of mid.
Actually, most
products
are kind
of mid,
which means
they don't
get
a review.
But
if something
is really,
really good,
oh, that's
interesting.
If something's
really, really
bad, sometimes
that's interesting
too.
So
you kind
of have
to find
what
is actually
interesting about
a product.
That's kind
of number
one.
And then
the rest
is, okay,
is there
a spot
for
it
on
the calendar?
Is there
a spot
for
it
on
the channel?
Are there
maybe other
videos
or topics
we've talked
about recently
that
can feed
into also
talking about
this new
thing?
So themes.
But yeah,
it's,
do I
want
to make
that video?
It's
the number
one thing.